http://www.consumercredit.com/privacy-policy

American Consumer Credit Counseling Privacy Policy – ConsumerCredit.com
Website Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, respond to a survey or fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, or phone number. What do we use this information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in any of the following ways:
To personalize your experienceYour information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
To improve our websiteWe continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
To improve customer serviceYour information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
To process transactionsYour information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
To send periodic emails or mail The email address or mailing address you provide may be used to send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
To contact by phoneThe phone number you provide may be used to contact you by phone, including on a mobile device using an auto-dialer/or text message. Wireless carrier fees may apply.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. We maintain your non-public personal information in accordance with our record retention guidelines.
Do we use cookies?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers’ hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer any of your personally identifiable information to outside parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Security
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as contact information, user names, and passwords) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using Secure Socket Layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If clients have any questions about the security at our Web site, clients can contact us at edu@consumercredit.com.
Opt-out
Our clients are given the opportunity to "opt-out" of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information. For example, our email newsletter has an opt-out mechanism so clients who do not want to be contacted via email will be taken off of our lists. To opt-out, send an email to edu@consumercredit.com.
Online Privacy policy only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Consent
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.
Changes to our privacy policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this page.
client PRIVACY POLICY
Facts:
What does American Consumer Credit Counseling, Inc. DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information.  Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing.  Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information.  Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
WHAT?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us.  This information can include:
Social Security number and credit card or other debt
Account balances and payment history
Income and checking account information
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
HOW?
All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business.  In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons American Consumer Credit Counseling, Inc. chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does American Consumer Credit Counseling, Inc. share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes – such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes – To offer our products and services to you
No
We don’t share
For joint marketing with other financial companies
No
We don’t share
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – Information about your transactions and experiences
No
We don’t share
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – Information about your creditworthiness
No
We don’t share
For nonaffiliates to market to you
No
We don’t share
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?
American Consumer Credit Counseling, Inc.
What we do
How does American Consumer Credit Counseling, Inc. protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.  These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does American Consumer Credit Counseling, Inc. collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Provide account information or give us your income information
Pay us by check or give us your contact information
Give us your employment history
We also collect your information from other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
Affiliates from using your information to market to you
Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control.  They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
American Consumer Credit Counseling, Inc. has no affiliates.
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control.  They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
American Consumer Credit Counseling, Inc. does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
American Consumer Credit Counseling, Inc. doesn’t jointly market.
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.
American Consumer Credit Counseling130 Rumford Ave, Suite 202Auburndale, Massachusetts 02466
info@consumercredit.com
800-769-3571
American Consumer Credit Counseling, Inc designated Copyright Agent is:
Katie Ross130 Rumford Ave, Suite 202Auburndale, Massachusetts 02466
kross@consumercredit.com
617-559-5700
Debt Relief
Credit Counseling
Debt Management Program
Debt Consolidation
Debt Settlement
Bankruptcy
LinkedIn
American Consumer Credit Counseling (ACCC) is a nonprofit organization offering free credit counseling sessions for consumers throughout the country. For anyone considering debt settlement program or working with credit card settlement companies, our counselors can explain the details of the credit card settlement process, discuss the debt settlement credit impact, outline the worst and best debt settlement scenarios and discuss other pros and cons of debt settlement. We can also help consumers explore the benefits of a debt management plan vs debt settlement, and answer questions like “How bad does debt settlement hurt credit?” and “Is debt settlement a good idea?” as well as “Does debt settlement work?”
Site Map
Careers
Privacy Policy
Licenses & Disclosures
Feedback
Contact
©2020 American Consumer Credit Counseling, Inc. 130 Rumford Ave, Suite 202, Auburndale, MA 02466
©2020 American Consumer Credit Counseling, Inc. 130 Rumford Ave, Suite 202, Auburndale, MA 02466
×
Client Login
©2020 American Consumer Credit Counseling, Inc. 130 Rumford Ave, Suite 202, Auburndale, MA 02466
